# Eric Lekwane | Student

Location: Tembisa

Cellphone: (+27) 84 439 4032 Email: u12318958@tuks.co.za

## Summary

Motivated young professional with an exemplary academic record possessing the dedication and passion to progress in applying complex mathematical models to the real world to solve real world problems.

Able to utilize strong mathematical skills, team orientation and interpersonal strengths to provide high quality services to the organization, 4th year Industrial engineering student with 1 + years of experience in design, programming, facilities planning, project management and supply chain management, possessing an indepth and technical understanding of Microsoft solutions, technologies and full Microsoft package. SAPS, Anylogic and Solid Works accredited, multi-lingual, self-motivated and with the zeal to achieve any goal.

### Skills and achievements

#### Core Skills:

- Python Creative Design MS Access MS Word, Excel, Power P Java C# & R Dart Solid Works Calculus/Statistics Numerical Analysis IsiZulu English SAPS Algebra Facilities Planning Setswana Any Logic Supply Chain Accounting **Project Management** 
  - **Certificates and Accreditations:**
- **SAPS** Certificate Jul 2016 - Nov 2016 Anylogic and Solid Works Accreditation Jul 2018 - Nov 2018

### **Education**

**Senior Secondary School**: Zitikeni Secondary (Located Gauteng)

Jan 2007 - Complete

#### **Subject Passed-Grade 12:**

1. Physical Sciences

2. Pure Mathematics

3. Life Sciences

4. Geography

Life Orientations

6. English (1st additional Lang)

7. IsiZulu (Home Lang)

**Institution**: University of Pretoria (Located Gauteng)

Jan 2012 - Current

Course: B.Eng. Industrial Systems 4th year

# **Experience**

### **University of Pretoria (Contract, Project)**

Python Programming Tutor (Contract)

Jan 2016 - Nov 2016

- JCP201 (Community Based Project)
- Introduction to python programing tutor, assisted students on and off campus with the basics of python programing, tracking students' progress with 100 % accuracy and obtaining a 94 % pass rate.
- Facilitated and managed a project were a large community dumping site was successfully cleaned.

## **Tiger Brands Ltd (Vacation Work)**

Jul 2016 - Aug 2016

Junior Process Manufacturing Engineer

- Focused on creating technical documents, applying ergonomics to the manufacturing facility.
- Focused on facilities planning and systems optimization, time studies.

# References are available on request